aop.com 2004-06-03

# Alpha Omega Publications - Privacy Policy

**Personal Information:**  
Alpha Omega Publications has instituted policies intended to ensure that your Personal Information (information which is personal to you or your child, such as name, address, email, telephone number, etc.) is maintained in a safe and responsible manner. We want you to know what type of information we collect and how it is maintained.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, we can be reached via email at: [privacy@aop.com](mailto:privacy@aop.com).

Alpha Omega Publications reserves the right in its sole discretion to modify this Privacy Policy at anytime. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on a frequent basis so that you understand our policies currently in effect. Please note this Privacy Policy applies to www.welcometoclass.com and www.aop.com only and not necessarily to affiliates and partners linked to the sites.

 **What We Collect:**  
Alpha Omega Publications may gather information about you for purposes of enrollment in the Academy, or to improve the content on our Web site and our product, for marketing, promotional, and other reasonable commercial purposes. Such data may include information gathered upon subscribing to our service, in response to surveys, or other requests for information.

We do not collect Personal Information about you unless you provide it voluntarily. We will not require disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary for participation in our services.

 **Monitoring Communications:**  
Communications on the site, such as chat room conversations and bulletin board messages, are logged on our servers. These logs are monitored to insure the safety of our students.

 **How We Use Your Information:**  
Alpha Omega Publications maintains all student data, student educational information and student files as confidential, which guards the privacy of Alpha Omega Academy students and families. We do not sell or share our student database. We have established strict security procedures to ensure that student files and information are not disclosed to unauthorized parties.

 **Cookies:**  
The WelcomeToClass web site makes limited use of "cookie" technology. A cookie is information about you that a web site sends to your browser. The information may be stored on your computer and later used to recognize you and your preferences. The use of this technology eliminates the repetitive need for students to re-enter identifying information at every sign-on.

WelcomeToClass uses temporary cookies to manage security during your sessions in WelcomeToClass.com. Cookie technology allows us to recognize you as a user and to manage security on the site. WelcomeToClass uses only random identifiers, without any student, parent or school information.

Please note, we do not dictate how our affiliates and partners linked to the Web site use cookies. On most commercial browsers, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which provides you with the opportunity to decide whether you want to accept or reject the cookie. When using WelcomeToClass.com, your browser must be set to accept our cookies or you will not be able to access the application.

 **Privacy Protection for Children:**  
Alpha Omega Academy urges parents and guardians to discuss with their children restrictions regarding the online release of Personal Information to anyone they don't know and to monitor their children's Internet activities. (See our Rules for Students, for more information.) We strive to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA).

Please read this Privacy Policy in its entirety to understand what Personal Information is collected from children on our Web site and how we use such information. We use best efforts to establish and maintain reasonable procedures to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information collected from children, although no assurances are provided.

No part of our Web site is specifically structured to attract children under the age of 13, except as a student enrolled in our Academy and under the guidance and supervision of an adult. Parental/Guardian consent is required in order for any child under 13 years of age to submit Personal Information to the Web site, and before Alpha Omega Academy will use or disclose that Personal Information. Only a parent or guardian may register a child for access to WelcomeToClass.com.

We will provide to a parent or guardian, upon proper request and identification, the following information about their child: (i) a description of the specific types of personal information collected from the child, and (ii) the opportunity at any time to refuse further use or future online collection of Personal Information from that child. We request the parent or guardian contact us via e-mail: [privacy@aop.com](mailto:privacy@aop.com), U.S. mail or facsimile with a sufficiently detailed request for information or notice, referring to contact information below. Certain exceptions may apply to the foregoing provisions, pursuant to COPPA and other applicable law.

If you are a teacher, school administrator, tutor or similar party, entering information about children, you represent that you have proper authority to submit the child's personal information, and agree to hold harmless Alpha Omega Academy from any and all claims relating to the acceptance and use of such information.

 **How to Contact Us:**  
We hope this Privacy Policy provides sufficient information about our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information. If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions, we invite you to contact us immediately. 

**  
Alpha Omega Academy**  
 **Attn: Marilyn Schlitz**  
 **300 N McKemy Ave**  
 **Chandler, AZ 85226**  
 **Phone: 480-735-7800**  
 **Fax: 480-893-6112**
